+++ 🌐 Live site of Minim.Clock : https://shubhgw.github.io/Minimalistic-clock/ +++

# 🙏 Welcome to the R
EADME file of Minimalistic clock 🙏!

🧑‍💻 I have many clocks but they got backfired somewhere , So to keep it simple, Minimalistic, easy to navigate I made this clock ( to be clear...... There is some work of Gemini)

✅ For now It show Live time of the System .
✅ Have four themes to get better visually !
✅ It have Three fonts styles .
➕ Later, A time toggle for 12hrs & 24hrs switch.
➕ Later, It will be able to set timer, count and set Alarms !

🙌 Thanks for the Visit , Please show support via gifting us !
